export const abhyazQuiz = {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "When was the Abhyaz platform launched?",
        choices: ["2011", "2012", "2020", "2018"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "2020",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the mission of the Abhyaz platform?",
        choices: [
          "To provide online courses on CNC, robotics, and automation",
          "To help people learn and grow in a variety of ways",
          "To partner with organizations like Siemens and Zoho",
          "To develop a skill development platform called SkillON365",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "To help people learn and grow in a variety of ways",
      },
      {
        question: "What type of training does Abhyaz offer?",
        choices: [
          "Only online courses",
          "Only virtual instructor-led training (VILT) sessions",
          "Both online courses and VILT sessions",
          "Only interactive courses",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Both online courses and VILT sessions",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of Abhyaz's skill development platform?",
        choices: ["SkillON365", "CNCTrain Library", "Enterprise Transformation", "Abhyaz eLearning"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "SkillON365",
      },
      {
        question: "What year did Abhyaz launch its CNCTrain Library?",
        choices: ["2019", "2020", "2022", "2023"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "2022",
      },
      {
        question: "What type of award has Abhyaz received?",
        choices: [
          "The NASSCOM Emerge 50 Award",
          "The Best eLearning Platform Award",
          "The Top 10 EdTech Companies Award",
          "The Most Innovative Learning Solution Award",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "The NASSCOM Emerge 50 Award",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the main area of knowledge covered by Abhyaz?",
        choices: [
          "Business and Management",
          "Engineering and Technology",
          "Healthcare and Medicine",
          "Arts and Humanities",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Engineering and Technology",
      },
      {
        question: "What type of learning content does Abhyaz offer?",
        choices: [
          "Textbooks and articles",
          "Videos and simulations",
          "Interactive exercises and assessments",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above",
      },
      {
        question: "Who uses the Abhyaz platform?",
        choices: ["Only individuals", "Only businesses", "Only educational institutions", "All of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the primary benefit of using Abhyaz?",
        choices: [
          "To earn a degree or certificate",
          "To learn new skills and knowledge",
          "To connect with other learners",
          "To find a job",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "To learn new skills and knowledge",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the current stage of the Abhyaz platform?",
        choices: ["A training center", "An eLearning platform", "A digital firm", "An enterprise transformation platform"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A digital firm",
      },
      {
        question: "How has Abhyaz evolved over time?",
        choices: [
          "It has become smaller and more focused.",
          "It has become larger and more diverse.",
          "It has remained the same.",
          "It has stopped offering some of its original services.",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "It has become larger and more diverse."
      }
    ]
}




export const resultInitalState = {
    score: 0,
    correctAnswers: 0,
    wrongAnswers: 0,
};

  